Guide to the Peter Palmquist Collection of Women in Photography
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Publication and Exhibition Research Files, Series III; (20 boxes)
  - Playing the Part: Depictions of Women Photographers, circa 2002-2003; (6 boxes)
    - Photocopies
      - Business cards (Box 443, Folder 3221)
    - Oversize Items
      - Glass negative, 1 glass negative and 1 photographic print (Box 444, Folder 3222)
        The mounted glass negative and a corresponding photographic print documents retouching techniques
      - Photograph album, 1 album (Box 445)
        Front board has an encapsulated photographic print depicting a woman and girl. Album contains no photographic prints.
      - Card photograph, 1 photographic print (Box 446, Folder 3223)
      - Copy photographs, 2 photographic prints (Box 446, Folder 3224)
      - Advertisements and illustrations, 20 tear sheets (Box 446, Folder 3225-3226)
  - Directory of the Pioneer Women Photographers of the World, circa 2002-2003; (1 box)
    This subseries consists of materials compiled circa 2002-2003 by Palmquist, Thomas R. Kailbourn, and Suzanna Urminska for a work documenting women photographers active before 1866. It consists of photocopies of primary and secondary printed materials with general information about early women photographers, collected materials about women employed as photographers during its formative years, and early fiction about photography.
    - Project description (Box 447, Folder 3227)
    - Research (Box 447, Folder 3228-3232)
    - Photography as employment (Box 447, Folder 3233-3234)
    - Fiction (Box 447, Folder 3235)
    - Illustrations (Box 447, Folder 3236)
  - Anonymous Early Women Photographers, circa 2002-2003; (1 box)
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by the title of the journal or work.
    This subseries consists of photocopies of printed materials for a publication project about anonymous women photographers in nineteenth century journals and books.
    - American Journal of Photography, circa 1860-1864 (Box 448, Folder 3237)
    - Art Union, 1840 (Box 448, Folder 3238)
    - Colorist, 1865 (Box 448, Folder 3239)
    - Daguerrean Journal, 1850 (Box 448, Folder 3240)
    - The Employments of Women, by Virginia Penny, circa 1863 (Box 448, Folder 3241)
    - Household Words: A Weekly Journal, 1853 (Box 448, Folder 3242)
    - The British Journal of Photography, 1860-1865 (Box 448, Folder 3243)
    - The London Times, 1847 (Box 448, Folder 3244)
    - Mustatine Tri-Weekly Journal, 1855 (Box 448, Folder 3245)
    - Nottingham Review, 1863 (Box 448, Folder 3246)
    - Philadelphia Photographer, 1865-1870 (Box 448, Folder 3247)
    - The Photographer and Fine Art Journal, 1854-1855 (Box 448, Folder 3248)
    - Photographic Art Journal, 1852-1853 (Box 448, Folder 3249)
    - The Photographic News, 1859-1870 (Box 448, Folder 3250)
    - Photographic Notes, 1856 (Box 448, Folder 3251)
    - Photographic World, 1871-1872 (Box 448, Folder 3252)
    - "Photography as an Employment for Women," in Englishwomen's Review of Social and Industrial Questions, 1867 (Box 448, Folder 3253)
    - San Francisco Daily Journal, 1850 (Box 448, Folder 3254)
    - Weekly Places Herald, 1852 (Box 448, Folder 3255)
    - Anonymous photographers in secondary sources (Box 448, Folder 3256)
    - Anonymous photographers according to Steve Knoblock, 1998 (Box 448, Folder 3257)
  - Photographs of Women, 2002-2003; (9 boxes)
    (580 photographic prints)
    This subseries is organized by physical format in six sections: Carte-de-visite photographs, Cabinet photographs, Stereographs, Photographic postcards, Other photographic formats, and Copy photographs. Items of each format are organized alphabetically by the surname or corporate name of photographers followed by photographs made by unidentified photographers.
    This subseries consists of photographs created by male photographers or unidentified photographers that depict women. Palmquist compiled these photographs in 2002-2003, probably for an exhibition about depictions of women in photographs.
    - Carte-de-visite photographs
      - Duvall, J. H., 1 photographic print (Box 449, Folder 3258)
      - Unidentified photographers
        - Images of women, 21 photographic prints (Box 449, Folder 3259)
        - Images of women with men, 2 photographic prints (Box 449, Folder 3260)
    - Cabinet Photographs
      - Abdullah Frères, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3261)
      - Allen, Ethan, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3262)
      - Alverson, Frank, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3263)
      - Anderson & Company, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3264)
      - Arcade Photo Company, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3265)
      - Augarten, N., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3266)
      - Austin, P. J., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3267)
      - Bain, W. E., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3268)
      - Barr, A. A., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3269)
      - Bell, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3270)
      - Boetcher & Lee, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3271)
      - Brand Studios, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3272)
      - Bristol, N. D., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3273)
      - Bugbee, F. E., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3274)
      - Burns, Thomas, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3275)
      - Burton & Cassels, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3276)
      - Bustrov, D. I., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3277)
      - Cain, C. E., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3278)
      - Cain, Elmer, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3279)
      - Call & Hurt, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3280)
      - Call, W. R., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3281)
      - Chickering, Elmer, 3 photographic prints (Box 450, Folder 3282)
      - Chickering, Walter E., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3283)
      - Clark, John C., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3284)
      - Clark, S. A., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3285)
      - Conant, D. J., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3286)
      - Cook, Theodore, 3 photographic prints (Box 450, Folder 3287)
      - Cramer Brothers, 3 photographic prints (Box 450, Folder 3288)
      - Critcherson, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3289)
      - Cutts, Perry, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3290)
      - Davidson, Isaac Grundy, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3291)
      - Demers & Son, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3292)
      - Dixon, S. J., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3293)
      - Dresser, 2 photographic prints (Box 450, Folder 3294)
      - Druse, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3295)
      - Elite Studio, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3296)
      - Elite Studio, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3297)
      - Evans, E. D., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3298)
      - Feiger & Son, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3299)
      - Fell, S. B., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3300)
      - Fidanza, F., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3301)
      - Freeman, G. W., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3302)
      - Gilhoussen, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3303)
      - Graves, T. L., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3304)
      - Gray, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3305)
      - Hardy, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3306)
      - Heath, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3307)
      - Hendee, Otho S., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3308)
      - Hindley, E. E., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3309)
      - Hirst, William, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3310)
      - Holgate, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3311)
      - Horne, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3312)
      - Howlett, I. E., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3313)
      - Hulse, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3314)
      - Ideal Studio, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3315)
      - Imperial, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3316)
      - Jensen, Carl, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3317)
      - Kenyon, F. P., & Son, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3318)
      - Koella, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3319)
      - Kopkuhal, B. E., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3320)
      - Kozin, N., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3321)
      - Kruse, A., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3322)
      - Kuzbatov, A., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3323)
      - Leonard's Studio, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3324)
      - Locke & Peterson, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3325)
      - Logan, Charles W., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3326)
      - Lonsbury, G. W., 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3327)
      - Loryea, Archibald, or Milton Loryea, 1 photographic print (Box 450, Folder 3328)
      - Mackey, H. C., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3329)
      - Martyn, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3330)
      - Maxwell, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3331)
      - McAlipn & Lamb, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3332)
      - McClure, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3333)
      - Mercer, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3334)
      - Mesch, August, Jr., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3335)
      - Montignani, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3336)
      - Mott, M. M., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3337)
      - Mundy, 2 photographic prints on 1 mount, 1 copy photographic print, and 2 copy negatives (Box 451, Folder 3338)
      - Nast, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3339)
      - Neidhardt, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3340)
      - Nelson, George P., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3341)
      - New York Gallery, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3342)
      - Newton Brothers, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3343)
      - Nickerson, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3344)
      - Notman Photo Company, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3345)
      - Nottingham, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3346)
      - Noyes, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3347)
      - Nyblin, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3348)
      - Ott, Frank H., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3349)
      - Palmquist, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3350)
      - Percival, Anthony, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3351)
      - Peterson, Louis, or Henry Peterson, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3352)
      - Pickett, W. B., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3353)
      - Pollen, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3354)
      - Postel, F., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3355)
      - Prophet, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3356)
      - Ralston, W., 2 photographic prints (Box 451, Folder 3357)
      - Rinehart, A. E., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3358)
      - Robinson, Fred, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3359)
      - Roeder, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3360)
      - Rommel, Eberhardt, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3361)
      - Rood, E. H., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3362)
      - Schemboche, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3363)
      - Scott & Company, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3364)
      - Shackett & Clauss, 2 photographic prints (Box 451, Folder 3365)
      - Singhi, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3366)
      - Sleyster, A. L., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3367)
      - Smith, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3368)
      - Smith, E. W., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3369)
      - Star Gallery, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3370)
      - Stevens, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3371)
      - Stroup's Gallery, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3372)
      - Swords Borthers, 2 photographic prints (Box 451, Folder 3373)
      - Tarasov, N. I., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3374)
      - Tate, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3375)
      - Thibault, Joseph, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3376)
      - Thompson & Son, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3377)
      - Thuss, A. J., and W. G. Thuss, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3378)
      - Towne, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3379)
      - Trunov, G. V., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3380)
      - Turtle, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3381)
      - Van Hoten, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3382)
      - Vanliew, A. J., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3383)
      - Vasidi, K., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3384)
      - Vasseur, L., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3385)
      - Viner, Fred, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3386)
      - Wagness, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3387)
      - Weber, F. William, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3388)
      - Wehe, Lewis E., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3389)
      - Weidner, G., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3390)
      - Wendt, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3391)
      - Wharton, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3392)
      - Wheeler, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3393)
      - White, E. A., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3394)
      - White, L., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3395)
      - Wilkinson, J., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3396)
      - Williar, C. C., 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3397)
      - Winter, 1 photographic print (Box 451, Folder 3398)
      - Unidentified photographers
        - Funeral flower arrangment, accompanied by a printed poem by E. C. Sherburne, 1 photographic print (Box 452, Folder 3399)
        - Mourning card for Louella C. Wilson (1842-1888), 1 piece of ephemera (Box 452, Folder 3400)
        - Images of women and girls, 14 photographic prints (Box 452, Folder 3401)
        - Images of women, girls, and men, 4 photographic prints (Box 452, Folder 3402)
    - Stereographs
      - Barker, George, 1 photographic print (Box 453, Folder 3403)
      - Graves, Carleton H., 1 photographic print (Box 453, Folder 3404)
      - Griffith, George W., 1 photographic print (Box 453, Folder 3405)
      - Kilburn, Benjamin West, 2 photographic prints (Box 453, Folder 3406)
      - Melander & Brother, 1 photographic print (Box 453, Folder 3407)
      - Rau, William Herman, 1 photographic print (Box 453, Folder 3408)
      - Strohmeyer & Wyman, 3 photographic prints (Box 453, Folder 3409)
      - Underwood & Underwood, 2 photographic prints (Box 453, Folder 3410)
      - Weller, Franklin G., 3 photographic prints (Box 453, Folder 3411)
      - White, Hawley C., 1 photographic print (Box 453, Folder 3412)
      - Unidentified creators, 6 photographic prints (Box 453, Folder 3413)
    - Postcards
      - A.B.C., 1 photographic print (Box 454, Folder 3414)
      - A. L., 1 photographic print (Box 454, Folder 3415)
      - Bowman, W. S., 1 photographic print (Box 454, Folder 3416)
      - Chekhovski, V., 1 photographic print (Box 454, Folder 3417)
      - Electric Studio, 1 photographic print (Box 454, Folder 3418)
      - F.K., 1 photographic print (Box 454, Folder 3419)
      - Gale's Studio, 1 photographic print (Box 454, Folder 3420)
      - G. L. Co., 2 photographic prints (Box 454, Folder 3421)
      - Lola, 1 photographic print (Box 454, Folder 3422)
      - Monroe, 1 photographic print (Box 454, Folder 3423)
      - Reutlinger, 2 photographic print (Box 454, Folder 3424)
      - S. C., 1 photographic print (Box 454, Folder 3425)
      - Van Graven, P., 1 photographic print (Box 454, Folder 3426)
      - Unidentified creators
        - Image of Alberta Claire, 1 photographic print and 1 tear sheet (Box 454, Folder 3427)
        - Portrait of Lillian and Mary Johnston, 1 photographic print (Box 454, Folder 3428)
        - Images of unidentified women
          - Exteriors, 16 photographic prints (Box 454, Folder 3429)
          - Exteriors with children, 15 photographic prints (Box 454, Folder 3430)
          - Exteriors with men, 9 photographic prints (Box 454, Folder 3431)
          - Interiors with children, 1 photographic print (Box 454, Folder 3432)
          - Studio portraits, 18 photographic prints (Box 454, Folder 3433)
          - Studio portraits with children, 14 photographic prints (Box 454, Folder 3434)
          - Studio portraits with men, 4 photographic prints (Box 454, Folder 3435)
    - Other photographic formats
      This section includes unmounted photographic prints and photographic prints in studio folders.
      - Alley Studio, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3436)
      - Aaberg Studio, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3437)
      - Arless, George Charles, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3438)
      - Blunck Studio, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3439)
      - Brisbois, Alfred, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3440)
      - Brown Studio, 4 photographic prints (Box 455, Folder 3441)
      - Bushnell, 2 photographic prints (Box 455, Folder 3442)
      - California Nursery, 16 photographic prints (Box 455, Folder 3443)
      - Chapman, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3444)
      - Climax Photo, 2 photographic prints (Box 455, Folder 3445)
      - Coleman, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3446)
      - Davies, George W., 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3447)
      - Dietz Studio, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3448)
      - Gebhardt & Company, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3449)
      - Grasshoff, F., 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3450)
      - Grove, C. Elmore, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3451)
      - Holborn, Henry, 2 photographic prints (Box 455, Folder 3452)
      - Hill, Andrew Putnam, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3453)
      - Keller, 2 photographic prints (Box 455, Folder 3454)
      - Landes, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3455)
      - Langhans, Jan, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3456)
      - Martin-Tucker, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3457)
      - Meander, Silas Peter, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3458)
      - Miller, William E., 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3459)
      - Montminy, M. A., 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3460)
      - Moreno, A., 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3461)
      - Moulton-Erickson, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3462)
      - Munro, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3463)
      - National Prosthetic Institute, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3464)
      - Planetary Photo, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3465)
      - Rice, Lewis, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3466)
      - Schell, 2 photographic prints (Box 455, Folder 3467)
      - Standen, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3468)
      - Sweney, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3469)
      - Wangsness, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3470)
      - Webb, Sidney L. (Box 455, Folder 3471)
      - Wellman, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3472)
      - Unidentified creators
        - Aftermath of an earthquake in Charleston, South Carolina, 2 photographic prints (Box 455, Folder 3473)
        - Portrait of Winifred Price, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3474)
        - Portrait of Mary Ann Purkis on a memorial card, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3475)
        - Portrait of Laura Sargent, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3476)
        - Portrait of Conrad and Tresa Schellpepper, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3477)
        - Portrait of Daisy Schute, 1 photographic print (Box 455, Folder 3478)
        - Portrait of a woman and a copy photograph of a letter by Charles William Shirley Brooks, 2 photographic prints (Box 455, Folder 3479)
        - Exterior images of women, 50 photographic prints (Box 456, Folder 3480)
        - Exterior images of women with children, 27 photographic prints (Box 456, Folder 3481)
        - Exterior images of women with men, 27 photographic prints (Box 456, Folder 3482)
        - Interior images of women, 5 photographic prints (Box 456, Folder 3483)
        - Interior images of women with children, 2 photographic prints (Box 456, Folder 3484)
        - Interior images of women with men, 1 photographic print (Box 456, Folder 3485)
        - Studio portraits of women, 80 photographic prints (Box 456, Folder 3486)
        - Studio portraits of women with children, 17 photographic prints (Box 456, Folder 3487)
        - Studio portraits of women with men, 7 photographic prints (Box 456, Folder 3488)
    - Copy photographs
      - Loryea, Archibald, or Milton Loryea, 1 photographic print (Box 457, Folder 3489)
      - Ragsdale, M. C., 1 photographic print (Box 457, Folder 3490)
      - Strong, 1 photographic print (Box 457, Folder 3491)
      - Unidentified creators
        - Exterior images of women, 10 photographic prints (Box 457, Folder 3492)
        - Exterior images of women with children, 5 photographic prints (Box 457, Folder 3493)
        - Exterior images of women with men, 9 photographic prints (Box 457, Folder 3494)
        - Interior images of women, 1 photographic print (Box 457, Folder 3495)
        - Interior images of women with children, 6 photographic prints (Box 457, Folder 3496)
        - Interior images of women with men, 1 photographic print (Box 457, Folder 3497)
        - Studio portraits of women, 18 photographic prints (Box 457, Folder 3498)
        - Studio portraits of women with children, 14 photographic prints (Box 457, Folder 3499)
        - Studio portraits of women with men, 8 photographic prints (Box 457, Folder 3500)
- Women in Photography International Records, 1980-2003; Series IV; (14 boxes)
  This series is organized into two subseries: Records and Event Materials.
  This series documents the activities of the Women in Photography International, including its membership, publications, and activities.
  Much of the biographical and photographic materials collected by the organization in the course of developing exhibitions were placed by Palmquist and his assistants in the corresponding biographical and photographic components of the Peter Palmquist Collection of Women in Photography.
  - Records
    This subseries is organized by format with volumes and loose records followed by publications.
    This subseries consists mainly of the records of Women in Photography International, including volumes of records bound by Palmquist, a small group of loose records, and publications of the organization, including a printout of its web site.
    - Volumes
      - Women in Photography International: Records, 1980-1993, compiled by E. K. Waller and Nancy Clendaniel, Directors
        - Volume 1. Legal and Financial; Membership, 1980-1993 (Box 458)
        - Volume 2. Correspondence and Notes, 1980-1993 (Box 459)
        - Volume 3. Correspondence with Photographers, 1980-1993 (Box 460)
        - Volume 4. Exhibitions, 1980-1993 (Box 461)
    - Loose Records
      - Layouts of brochures and stationery, undated (Box 462, Folder 3501)
      - Form letters, circa 1985-1990 (Box 462, Folder 3502)
      - Panel proposal for the annual meeting of the Society of Photographic Educators in Boulder, Colorado, 1991 (Box 462, Folder 3503)
    - Publications
      - Women in Photography Bi-Monthly Bulletin, 1982 Nov-1988 Apr (Box 462, Folder 3504)
      - f2: Women in Photography, 1988 Winter-1992 Winter (Box 462, Folder 3505)
        Includes a printout of a electronic mail message by Nancy Clendaniel that outlines the publication history of f2, as well as copy photographs created of images for an issue and an advertising rate schedule
      - Printout of the Women in Photography International website, 2003 Jun 10 (Box 462, Folder 3506)
  - Event Materials